Connie Regan-Blake collection, 1974-2014
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 3: Graphic Images, ca. 1969-2007
  - Subseries B: Black-and-white negatives
    - Folktellers performances, 1975-1977, 7 31/2x3 in. black-and-white negatives; 7 images (Box-folder 32/5)
      Images of The Folktellers performing including images of the audience.
    - The Folktellers, 1980, 1986, 23 35mm black-and-white negative strips; 90 images (Box-folder 32/6)
      Images of The Folktellers publicity shots. Some of the images are labelled, 1980 and 1986.
    - Folktellers in Gillette, Wyoming, 1983, 7 35mm black-and-white negative strips; 34 images (Box-folder 32/7)
      Images of The Folktellers in Wyoming.
    - The Folktellers, undated, 2 5x7 in. black-and-white negatives; 2 images (Box-folder 32/8)
      Images of The Folktellers publicity shots for a publication cover.
    - The Folktellers, undated, 7 35mm black-and-white negative strips; 31 images (Box-folder 32/9)
    - The Folktellers, undated, 1 4x5 in. copy negative; 1 35mm black-and-white negative strip; 3 images (Box-folder 32/10)
      Images of The Folktellers publicity shots.
    - The Folktellers, undated, 1 35mm black-and-white negative strip; 2 images (Box-folder 32/11)
    - The Folktellers, undated, 3 35mm black-and-white negative strips; 18 images (Box-folder 32/12)
      Images of The Folktellers on the set of Mountain sweet talk. Also includes images of the Folktellers in the dressing room.
    - The Folktellers, undated, 7 35mm black-and-white negative strips; 35 images (Box-folder 32/13)
      Includes images of The Folktellers on the set of Mountain sweet talk. Also includes publicity shots.
    - The Folktellers, undated, 4 120mm black-and-white negative strips; 12 images (Box-folder 32/14)
      Includes images of The Folktellers publicity shots.
    - The Folktellers, undated, 4 120mm black-and-white negative strips; 12 images (Box-folder 32/15)
    - The Folktellers, undated, 4 120mm black-and-white negative strips; 12 images (Box-folder 32/16)
    - The Folktellers, undated, 1 35mm black-and-white negative strip (Box-folder 32/17)
    - The Folktellers, undated, 1 35mm black-and-white negative strip; 2 images (Box-folder 32/18)
    - The Folktellers, undated, 1 35mm black-and-white negative strip; 5 images (Box-folder 32/19)
    - The Folktellers published materials, undated, 8 35mm black-and-white negative strips; 3 images (Box-folder 32/20)
      Includes images of The Folktellers published materials.
    - Healer and Philippines, 1985, 2 35mm black-and-white negative strips; 21 images (Box-folder 32/21)
      Images of individuals in a room.
    - Mountain sweet talk, undated, 1 35mm black-and-white negative strip; 4 images (Box-folder 32/22)
      Includes images of The Folktellers on the set of their play.
    - Mountain sweet talk, undated, 1 35mm black-and-white negative strip; 4 images (Box-folder 32/23)
    - Mountain sweet talk, undated, 7 35mm black-and-white negative strips; 26 images (Box-folder 32/24)
    - Mountain sweet talk, undated, 2 35mm black-and-white negative strips; 8 images (Box-folder 32/25)
    - Mountain sweet talk, undated, 6 35mm black-and-white negative strips; 16 images (Box-folder 32/26)
    - Mountain sweet talk and the Folktellers, 1984-1988, 8 35mm black-and-white negative strips; 23 images (Box-folder 32/27)
      Includes images of The Folktellers on the set of their play. Also includes the publicity shots used for creating their posters. There are also images of The Folktellers at the Stone House, 1984.
    - Mountain sweet talk set, 1985, 7 35 35mm black-and-white negative strips; 23 images (Box-folder 32/28)
    - Mountain sweet talk, staged promo, 1987, 9 35mm black-and-white negative strips; 42 images (Box-folder 32/29)
      Includes images of The Folktellers on the set of their play. Also includes publicity shots taken on the stage.
    - Mountain sweet talk set, 1990 (1 of 2), 1 35mm black-and-white negative strip; 4 images (Box-folder 32/30)
    - Mountain sweet talk, 1990 (2 of 2), 14 35mm black-and-white negatives strips; 69 images (Box-folder 32/31)
    - John Basinger, 1979 undated, 6 35mm black-and-white; 19 images (Box-folder 32/32)
      Includes images of John Basinger who voiced for Sam Edwards and Bernard Bragg who were deaf storytellers.
  - Subseries C: Color slides
    - Connie Regan-Blake, 1976, 1 35mm color slide (Box-folder 33/1)
      Images of Connie Regan-Blake performing at a festival.
    - The Folktellers, 1979, 10 35mm color slides (Box-folder 33/2)
      Images of The Folktellers posing with stage props.
    - The Folktellers, 1981, 7 35mm color slides (Box-folder 33/3)
    - The Folktellers, 1984, 13 35mm color slides (Box-folder 33/4)
      Images of The Folktellers in 1984.
    - The Folktellers magazine cover slides, 1984-1985, 4 35mm color slides (Box-folder 33/5)
      Images of a magazine cover featuring The Folktellers. Also includes images of The Folktellers publicity shots.
    - The Folktellers magazine covers, 1985, 16 35mm color slides (Box-folder 33/6)
      Images of the magazine covers featuring The Folktellers.
    - The Folktellers and Mountain sweet talk, 1984-undated, 6 35mm color slides (Box-folder 33/7)
      Includes images of The Folktellers performing their play. Also includes publicity shots.
    - The Folktellers, State College, Pennsylvania, undated, 3 35mm color slides (Box-folder 33/8)
      Images of The Folktellers at State College in Pennsylvania.
    - Mountain sweet talk, 1986, 4 35mm color slides (Box-folder 33/9)
      Images of The Folktellers performing their play.
    - Mountain sweet talk, 1986, 6 35mm color slides (Box-folder 33/10)
    - Mountain sweet talk, 1986-1987, 4 35mm color slides (Box-folder 33/11)
    - Mountain sweet talk, 1986, 10 35mm color slides (Box-folder 33/12)
      Includes images of The Folktellers performing their play. Also includes images of publicity shots.
    - Mountain sweet talk, 1987, 7 35mm color slides (Box-folder 33/13)
      Includes images of The Folktellers performing their play. Also includes images of The Folktellers performing at events.
    - Mountain sweet talk, 1988, 18 35mm color slides (Box-folder 33/14)
      Includes images of publicity shots from the play. A note indicates the images were taken by Mary Jo Brezny, 1988.
    - Mountain sweet talk, 1990, 1 35mm color slides (Box-folder 33/15)
    - Unidentified location, undated, 1 35mm color slide (Box-folder 33/16)
      Landscape photographs of an unidentified location. The images have a church steeple in the background.
  - Subseries D: Black-and-white photographs
    - The Folktellers performing, 1976, undated, 34 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 34/1)
      Photographs of The Folktellers performing at events including publicity photographs. One image shows Connie looking at a map. Some of the images are identified as 1976 while the vast majority are undated.
    - Folktellers performing, undated, 4 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 34/2)
      Photographs of Connie Regan-Blake performing solo and as part of The Folktellers. Also includes black-and-white publicity photographs.
    - The Folktellers, 1981, 9 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 34/3)
      Photographs of The Folktellers in their famous pick up truck. Also includes images of The Folktellers performing at a school along with publicity photographs.
    - The Folktellers, 1983, 1 black-and-white print (Box-folder 34/4)
      Includes a publicity photograph of The Folktellers. Photo taken by David Holt.
    - The Folktellers, 1983, undated, 12 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 34/5)
      Photographs of The Folktellers performing, as well as images of other performers and group photos. Also includes publicity photographs.
    - The Folktellers promo shoot, 1988, undated, 6 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 35/1)
      Publicity photographs of The Folktellers. One image shows the Folktellers sitting on a porch.
    - The Folktellers, undated, 4 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 35/2)
      Photographs of The Folktellers performing onstage. Also includes publicity photographs.
    - The Folktellers, undated, 2 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 35/3)
      Publicity photographs of The Folktellers.
    - The Folktellers, undated, 2 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 35/4)
      Publicity photographs of The Folktellers with the mountains in the background.
    - The Folktellers, undated, 2 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 35/5)
    - The Folktellers, undated, 4 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 35/6)
      Photographs of The Folktellers performing at an educational facility. Also include publicity photographs.
    - The Folktellers, undated, 2 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 35/7)
      Photographs of The Folktellers performing. Also includes publicity photographs.
    - The Folktellers, undated, 1 black-and-white print (Box-folder 35/8)
      Publicity photograph of The Folktellers.
    - The Folktellers, undated, 15 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 35/9)
    - The Folktellers with pets, undated, 1 black-and-white print (Box-folder 35/10)
      Photograph of The Folktellers holding a cat and a dog.
    - The Folktellers, undated, 2 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 35/11)
      Publicity photographs of The Folktellers including an image of the Folktellers in their pickup truck.
    - The Folktellers, undated, 20 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 35/12)
      Photographs of The Folktellers performing onstage including publicity photographs.
    - The Folktellers, undated, 2 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 35/13)
    - The Folktellers, undated, 16 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 35/14)
      Photographs of Connie Regan-Blake performing including publicity photographs.
    - The Folktellers publicity, undated, 4 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 35/15)
      Photographs of The Folktellers performing including publicity photographs.
    - Mountain sweet talk, 1983, undated, 42 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 36/1)
      Includes photographs of the set. Also includes publicity photographs of The Folktellers performing in front of an audience of children.
    - Mountain sweet talk, 1986, 3 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 36/2)
    - The Folktellers performing various plays, 1987-1988, undated, 19 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 36/3)
      Photographs of The Folktellers performing Mountain sweet talk and A penny a talk. Also includes publicity photographs.
    - Folktellers performing, 1988, undated, 8 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 36/4)
      Photographs of The Folktellers performing Mountain sweet talk. Also includes performance images of Connie Regan-Blake.
    - Mountain sweet talk, undated, 3 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 36/5)
      Includes photographs of The Folktellers performing onstage including a publicity photograph.
    - Mountain sweet talk, undated, 2 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 36/6)
      Photographs of The Folktellers onstage including a publicity photograph.
    - Mountain sweet talk, undated, 1 black-and-white print (Box-folder 36/7)
      Photograph of The Folktellers onstage.
    - Mountain sweet talk, undated, 2 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 36/8)
      Includes photographs of The Folktellers onstage.
    - Mountain sweet talk, undated, 1 black-and-white print (Box-folder 36/9)
      Includes a photograph of The Folktellers performing their play onstage.
    - Mountain sweet talk and CHS performance, 1990, undated, 23 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 36/10)
      Photographs of The Folktellers performing as well as images from the CHS performance. There is also a photograph of John Basinger.
    - Mountain sweet talk, undated, 2 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 36/11)
      Includes photographs of The Folktellers performing their play onstage. Also includes a photograph of the Folktellers in an earlier performance of the Trolls.
    - Mountain sweet talk, undated, 11 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 36/12)
      Photographs of The Folktellers performing onstage. Also includes images of an earlier performance along with publicity photographs.
    - Mountain sweet talk, undated, 1 black-and-white print (Box-folder 36/13)
      Photograph of The Folktellers performing onstage.
    - Mountain sweet talk, undated, 6 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 36/14)
      Includes photographs of The Folktellers performing onstage along with publicity photographs. There is also one image of the Folktellers in their pickup truck.
    - Mountain sweet talk, undated, 1 black-and-white print (Box-folder 36/15)
    - Mountain sweet talk, undated, 3 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 37/1)
      Photographs of The Folktellers onstage.
    - Mountain sweet talk, undated, 6 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 37/2)
      Photographs of The Folktellers performing their play.
    - Mountain sweet talk, undated, 27 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 37/3)
    - Mountain sweet talk, undated, 27 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 37/4)
    - Other Storytellers, 2 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 37/5)
      Images of storytellers, Ashley Bryan, and Chuck Larkin at the 1980 International Storytelling Festival, Jonesborough, Tennessee.
    - John Basinger, 14 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 37/6)
      Prints of John Basinger.
    - Barbara and Connie telling stories, 1964, 5 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 38/1)
      Images of Barbara Freeman telling stories to a group of individuals in Tennessee. Also includes photographs of Connie telling stories to an audience of children.
    - The Folktellers at Mariposa, 1978, 4 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 38/2)
      Photographs of The Folktellers performing at Mariposa. Also includes images of the crowd.
    - The Folktellers performing at various locations, 1980-1989, undated, 13 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 38/3)
      Photographs of The Folktellers performing at events. Photographs are dated 1980, 1987 and 1989-undated.
    - Folktellers performing, 1981-1989, 8 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 38/4)
      Images of The Folktellers performing at events 1981, 1988-1989.
    - The Folktellers performing 1983-1985, undated, 12 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 38/5)
      Includes photographs of The Folktellers performing including a promo shoot.
    - Folktellers at Festival, 1985, 2 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 38/6)
      Photographs of The Folktellers in the audience at a festival. Also includes a photograph of Connie Regan-Blake telling a story.
    - The Folktellers, Pontage, Michigan, 1985, 39 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 38/7)
      Includes photographs of The Folktellers participating in various activities from grocery store shopping to performing onstage. Original envelope indicates the photographs were taken by John in February, 1985, Pontage, Michigan.
    - The Folktellers performing, undated, 6 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 38/8)
      Photographs of The Folktellers performing at events.
    - Barbara performing, undated, 3 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 38/9)
      Photographs of Barbara performing. Also includes publicity photographs.
    - The Folktellers performing, undated, 3 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 38/10)
      Includes photographs of The Folktellers performing and participating at events. Also includes publicity photographs.
    - The Folktellers performing, undated, 11 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 38/11)
      Photographs of The Folktellers performing at events. Also includes publicity photographs.
    - The Folktellers performing, undated, 5 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 38/12)
      Photographs of The Folktellers onstage including an image of storyteller, John Stansfield.
    - The Folktellers performing, undated, 1 black-and-white print (Box-folder 38/13)
    - The Folktellers performing, undated, 4 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 38/14)
    - The Folktellers published materials, undated, 15 black-and-white prints (Box-folder 38/15)
      Photographs of The Folktellers published materials.
  - Subseries E: Color photographic prints
    - Bead for Life and workshop, 2007, undated, 4 color prints (Box-folder 39/1)
      Photographs of Connie Regan-Blake at her summer storytelling workshop. One image shows Connie in a kitchen assembling beads.
    - Connie Regan-Blake and the Elberts, 2005, 1 color print (Box-folder 39/2)
      Includes a photograph of Connie Regan-Blake with two individuals. The print is labelled, "The Elberts, MI, 12/05."
    - Connie Regan-Blake, Jacksonville, Florida, undated, 2 color prints (Box-folder 39/3)
      Includes group photographs.
    - Connie Regan-Blake, Pitkin County Library, undated, 2 color prints (Box-folder 39/4)
      Includes color photographs of Connie Regan-Blake.
    - Publicity photographs of children, 1969-1979, undated, 3 color prints (Box-folder 39/5)
      Publicity photographs of children. Each print has the name of the child and date of the photograph printed on the back.
    - The Folktellers, 1980, 88 color prints (Box-folder 39/6)
      Publicity photographs of the Folktellers on a bridge and in the meadows.
    - The Folktellers, publicity photographs, and Lockarms Stone House, 1984, 3 color prints (Box-folder 39/7)
      Includes publicity photographs of the Folktellers as well as images of the Lockarms Stone House.
    - The Folktellers, undated, 2 color prints (Box-folder 39/8)
      Publicity photographs of the Folktellers.
    - The Folktellers, International Storytelling Festival, 1990, undated, 9 color prints (Box-folder 39/9)
      Includes photographs of The Folktellers at the log cabin.
    - The Folktellers, 1980, 2 color prints (Box-folder 39/10)
    - The Folktellers, undated, 1 color print (Box-folder 39/11)
    - The Folktellers, undated, 22 color prints (Box-folder 39/12)
    - The Folktellers with Dr. Susan Brown, Ohio, 1980, 3 color prints (Box-folder 39/13)
      Labelled photographs of Dr. Susan Brown with The Folktellers.
    - The Folktellers performing, 1981, 2 color prints (Box-folder 39/14)
      Photographs of The Folktellers performing onstage.
    - Various school locations, 1983-1986, 7 color prints (Box-folder 39/15)
      Photographs of The Folktellers performing at elementary and high schools.
    - The Folktellers in Philadelphia, 1985, 2 color prints (Box-folder 39/16)
      Photographs of The Folktellers on the main stage at a festival.
    - Connie Regan-Blake with other storytellers, undated, 1 color print (Box-folder 39/17)
      Includes a photograph of Connie Regan posing with a group identified as "other tellers".
    - The Folktellers at Connie's house, undated, 1 color print (Box-folder 39/18)
      An image of The Folktellers at Connie Regan-Blake's house.
    - Stonecastle Party, 1986, 9 color prints (Box-folder 39/19)
      Photographs of Jimmy Neil Smith and staff at the Mountain sweet talk cast party.
    - Mountain sweet talk set, 1988, 24 color prints (Box-folder 40/1)
    - Mountain sweet talk, Washington Flyer magazine, undated, 4 color prints (Box-folder 40/2)
      Photographs of the Folktellers with Connie holding a banjo and Barbara with a lumberjack as they appeared at the Folk Art Center Theater. The photograph was loaned to the Washington Flyer magazine to be included in the September/October issue of the magazine.
    - Mountain sweet talk, cast and crew, undated (1 of 2), 42 color print (Box-folder 40/3)
      Photographs of The Folktellers and production crew on the set of the play.
    - Mountain sweet talk, cast and crew, undated (2 of 2), 104 color prints (Box-folder 40/4)
    - Mountain sweet talk, undated, 19 color prints (Box-folder 40/5)
    - Mountain sweet talk, undated, 2 color print (Box-folder 40/6)
    - Mountain sweet talk, undated, 22 color prints (Box-folder 40/7)
      Photographs of The Folktellers dancing while performing their play.
    - Mountain sweet talk, undated, 14 color prints (Box-folder 40/8)
      Photographs of The Folktellers performing onstage with props and playing the banjo.
    - Mountain sweet talk, undated, 51 color prints (Box-folder 40/9)
    - Mountain sweet talk, undated, 5 color print (Box-folder 40/10)
    - Mountain sweet talk, undated, 4 color prints (Box-folder 40/11)
      Photographs of The Folktellers on the set of their play. Includes photographs of the Folktellers in the dressing room.
    - Mountain sweet talk, undated, 1 color print (Box-folder 40/12)
      Publicity photograph of the Folktellers onstage. Connie holds a book while Barbara holds a candle.
    - Mountain sweet talk, undated, 7 color prints (Box-folder 40/13)
      Photographs on the set of the play including a group photo of The Folktellers onstage.
    - The Folktellers, undated, 1 color print (Box 44)
      Publicity photo. In oversize box 44.
  - Subseries F: Color contact sheets
    - Mountain sweet talk, undated, 3 sheets, 65 images, color (Box-folder 40/14)
      Photographs of The Folktellers on the set of the play including publicity photographs. See also folders 15/3 and 15/4 for corresponding photographs.
  - Subseries G: Black-and-white contact sheets
    - The Folktellers at Central Michigan University, 1984, 2 contact sheets; 64 black-and-white images (Box-folder 41/1)
      Images of The Folktellers performing at Central Michigan University.
    - The Folktellers at The International Storytelling Festival, 1984, 22 contact sheets; 638 black-and-white images (Box-folder 41/2)
      Images of storytellers who presented at the Festival. Storytellers include Jackie Torrence, Ed Stivender and many more. Photographs taken by Tom Raymond, Jonesborough, Tennessee.
    - Folktellers performing and publicity photographs, undated, 2 contact sheets; 33 black-and-white-images (Box-folder 41/3)
      Images of The Folktellers performing at events.
    - The Folktellers performing at various locations, undated, 10 contact sheets; 227 black-and-white images (Box-folder 41/4)
      Images of The Folktellers performing their play. Also includes a performance in Long Island, New York.
    - The Folktellers performing at various locations, undated, 7 contact sheets; 168 black-and-white images (Box-folder 41/5)
      Images of The Folktellers performing their play. Also includes The Folktellers performing at other events.
    - Mountain sweet talk set and publicity photographs, 1988 (1 of 2), 1 contact sheet; 33 black-and-white images (Box-folder 41/6)
      A scene from the play along with a promo shoot, July 10, 1988.
    - Mountain sweet talk set and publicity photographs, undated (2 of 2), 2 contact sheets; 41 black-and-white images (Box-folder 41/7)
      A scene from the play along with a promo shoot.
    - Mountain sweet talk and publicity photographs, undated, 1 contact sheet; 33 black-and-white images (Box-folder 41/8)
    - Mountain sweet talk, 1986-undated, 3 contact sheets, 50 black-and-white images (Box-folder 41/9)
      The Folktellers performing Mountain sweet talk.
- Series 4: Moving Images, 1980-2007
  - Storytelling: tales for children and techniques for teachers, 1 videocassette (VHS; 60 min.): analog. (Item-id AFC 2015/003: MV01)
    1 videocassette of Barbara Freeman and Connie Regan-Blake telling children's stories as well as performing at an in-service workshop for teachers, parents and librarians, 1994.
  - Storytelling: tales for children and techniques for teachers, 1 videocassette (VHS; 60 min.): analog. (Item-id AFC 2015/003: MV02)
    The original preview recording of Tales and Techniques entertaining workshop by Barbara Freeman and Connie Regan-Blake telling children's stories as well an performing an in-service workshop for teachers, parents and librarians. Recorded by PBS in Knoxville, Tennessee.
  - Pennies, pets, and peanut butter: stories for children 1994, 1 videocassette (VHS; 30 min.): analog. (Item-id AFC 2015/003: MV03)